
name                                                                                         date       venue          
----                                                                                         ----       -----          
Chennai Super Kings vs Delhi Capitals, 18th Match, Indian Premier League 2026                2026-04-11 MA Chidambar...
Chennai Super Kings vs Gujarat Titans, 66th Match, Indian Premier League 2026                2026-05-21 MA Chidambar...
Chennai Super Kings vs Kolkata Knight Riders, 22nd Match, Indian Premier League 2026         2026-04-14 MA Chidambar...
Chennai Super Kings vs Lucknow Super Giants, 53rd Match, Indian Premier League 2026          2026-05-10 MA Chidambar...
Chennai Super Kings vs Mumbai Indians, 44th Match, Indian Premier League 2026                2026-05-02 MA Chidambar...
Chennai Super Kings vs Punjab Kings, 7th Match, Indian Premier League 2026                   2026-04-03 MA Chidambar...
Chennai Super Kings vs Sunrisers Hyderabad, 63rd Match, Indian Premier League 2026           2026-05-18 MA Chidambar...
Delhi Capitals vs Chennai Super Kings, 48th Match, Indian Premier League 2026                2026-05-05 Arun Jaitley...
Delhi Capitals vs Gujarat Titans, 14th Match, Indian Premier League 2026                     2026-04-08 Arun Jaitley...
Delhi Capitals vs Kolkata Knight Riders, 51st Match, Indian Premier League 2026              2026-05-08 Arun Jaitley...
Delhi Capitals vs Mumbai Indians, 8th Match, Indian Premier League 2026                      2026-04-04 Arun Jaitley...
Delhi Capitals vs Punjab Kings, 35th Match, Indian Premier League 2026                       2026-04-25 Arun Jaitley...
Delhi Capitals vs Rajasthan Royals, 62nd Match, Indian Premier League 2026                   2026-05-17 Arun Jaitley...
Delhi Capitals vs Royal Challengers Bengaluru, 39th Match, Indian Premier League 2026        2026-04-27 Arun Jaitley...
Gujarat Titans vs Chennai Super Kings, 37th Match, Indian Premier League 2026                2026-04-26 Narendra Mod...
Gujarat Titans vs Kolkata Knight Riders, 25th Match, Indian Premier League 2026              2026-04-17 Narendra Mod...
Gujarat Titans vs Mumbai Indians, 30th Match, Indian Premier League 2026                     2026-04-20 Narendra Mod...
Gujarat Titans vs Punjab Kings, 46th Match, Indian Premier League 2026                       2026-05-03 Narendra Mod...
Gujarat Titans vs Rajasthan Royals, 9th Match, Indian Premier League 2026                    2026-04-04 Narendra Mod...
Gujarat Titans vs Royal Challengers Bengaluru, 42nd Match, Indian Premier League 2026        2026-04-30 Narendra Mod...
Gujarat Titans vs Sunrisers Hyderabad, 56th Match, Indian Premier League 2026                2026-05-12 Narendra Mod...
Kolkata Knight Riders vs Delhi Capitals, 70th Match, Indian Premier League 2026              2026-05-24 Eden Gardens...
Kolkata Knight Riders vs Gujarat Titans, 60th Match, Indian Premier League 2026              2026-05-16 Eden Gardens...
Kolkata Knight Riders vs Lucknow Super Giants, 15th Match, Indian Premier League 2026        2026-04-09 Eden Gardens...
Kolkata Knight Riders vs Mumbai Indians, 65th Match, Indian Premier League 2026              2026-05-20 Eden Gardens...
Kolkata Knight Riders vs Punjab Kings, 12th Match, Indian Premier League 2026                2026-04-06 Eden Gardens...
Kolkata Knight Riders vs Rajasthan Royals, 28th Match, Indian Premier League 2026            2026-04-19 Eden Gardens...
Kolkata Knight Riders vs Sunrisers Hyderabad, 6th Match, Indian Premier League 2026          2026-04-02 Eden Gardens...
Lucknow Super Giants vs Chennai Super Kings, 59th Match, Indian Premier League 2026          2026-05-15 Bharat Ratna...
Lucknow Super Giants vs Delhi Capitals, 5th Match, Indian Premier League 2026                2026-04-01 Bharat Ratna...
Lucknow Super Giants vs Gujarat Titans, 19th Match, Indian Premier League 2026               2026-04-12 Bharat Ratna...
Lucknow Super Giants vs Kolkata Knight Riders, 38th Match, Indian Premier League 2026        2026-04-26 Bharat Ratna...
Lucknow Super Giants vs Punjab Kings, 68th Match, Indian Premier League 2026                 2026-05-23 Bharat Ratna...
Lucknow Super Giants vs Rajasthan Royals, 32nd Match, Indian Premier League 2026             2026-04-22 Bharat Ratna...
Lucknow Super Giants vs Royal Challengers Bengaluru, 50th Match, Indian Premier League 2026  2026-05-07 Bharat Ratna...
Mumbai Indians vs Chennai Super Kings, 33rd Match, Indian Premier League 2026                2026-04-23 Wankhede Sta...
Mumbai Indians vs Kolkata Knight Riders, 2nd Match, Indian Premier League 2026               2026-03-29 Wankhede Sta...
Mumbai Indians vs Lucknow Super Giants, 47th Match, Indian Premier League 2026               2026-05-04 Wankhede Sta...
Mumbai Indians vs Punjab Kings, 24th Match, Indian Premier League 2026                       2026-04-16 Wankhede Sta...
Mumbai Indians vs Rajasthan Royals, 69th Match, Indian Premier League 2026                   2026-05-24 Wankhede Sta...
Mumbai Indians vs Royal Challengers Bengaluru, 20th Match, Indian Premier League 2026        2026-04-12 Wankhede Sta...
Mumbai Indians vs Sunrisers Hyderabad, 41st Match, Indian Premier League 2026                2026-04-29 Wankhede Sta...
Punjab Kings vs Delhi Capitals, 55th Match, Indian Premier League 2026                       2026-05-11 Himachal Pra...
Punjab Kings vs Gujarat Titans, 4th Match, Indian Premier League 2026                        2026-03-31 Maharaja Yad...
Punjab Kings vs Lucknow Super Giants, 29th Match, Indian Premier League 2026                 2026-04-19 Maharaja Yad...
Punjab Kings vs Mumbai Indians, 58th Match, Indian Premier League 2026                       2026-05-14 Himachal Pra...
Punjab Kings vs Rajasthan Royals, 40th Match, Indian Premier League 2026                     2026-04-28 Maharaja Yad...
Punjab Kings vs Royal Challengers Bengaluru, 61st Match, Indian Premier League 2026          2026-05-17 Himachal Pra...
Punjab Kings vs Sunrisers Hyderabad, 17th Match, Indian Premier League 2026                  2026-04-11 Maharaja Yad...
Rajasthan Royals vs Chennai Super Kings, 3rd Match, Indian Premier League 2026               2026-03-30 Barsapara Cr...
Rajasthan Royals vs Delhi Capitals, 43rd Match, Indian Premier League 2026                   2026-05-01 Sawai Mansin...
Rajasthan Royals vs Gujarat Titans, 52nd Match, Indian Premier League 2026                   2026-05-09 Sawai Mansin...
Rajasthan Royals vs Lucknow Super Giants, 64th Match, Indian Premier League 2026             2026-05-19 Sawai Mansin...
Rajasthan Royals vs Mumbai Indians, 13th Match, Indian Premier League 2026                   2026-04-07 Barsapara Cr...
Rajasthan Royals vs Royal Challengers Bengaluru, 16th Match, Indian Premier League 2026      2026-04-10 Barsapara Cr...
Rajasthan Royals vs Sunrisers Hyderabad, 36th Match, Indian Premier League 2026              2026-04-25 Sawai Mansin...
Royal Challengers Bengaluru vs Chennai Super Kings, 11th Match, Indian Premier League 2026   2026-04-05 M.Chinnaswam...
Royal Challengers Bengaluru vs Delhi Capitals, 26th Match, Indian Premier League 2026        2026-04-18 M.Chinnaswam...
Royal Challengers Bengaluru vs Gujarat Titans, 34th Match, Indian Premier League 2026        2026-04-24 M.Chinnaswam...
Royal Challengers Bengaluru vs Kolkata Knight Riders, 57th Match, Indian Premier League 2026 2026-05-13 Shaheed Veer...
Royal Challengers Bengaluru vs Lucknow Super Giants, 23rd Match, Indian Premier League 2026  2026-04-15 M.Chinnaswam...
Royal Challengers Bengaluru vs Mumbai Indians, 54th Match, Indian Premier League 2026        2026-05-10 Shaheed Veer...
Royal Challengers Bengaluru vs Sunrisers Hyderabad, 1st Match, Indian Premier League 2026    2026-03-28 M.Chinnaswam...
Sunrisers Hyderabad vs Chennai Super Kings, 27th Match, Indian Premier League 2026           2026-04-18 Rajiv Gandhi...
Sunrisers Hyderabad vs Delhi Capitals, 31st Match, Indian Premier League 2026                2026-04-21 Rajiv Gandhi...
Sunrisers Hyderabad vs Kolkata Knight Riders, 45th Match, Indian Premier League 2026         2026-05-03 Rajiv Gandhi...
Sunrisers Hyderabad vs Lucknow Super Giants, 10th Match, Indian Premier League 2026          2026-04-05 Rajiv Gandhi...
Sunrisers Hyderabad vs Punjab Kings, 49th Match, Indian Premier League 2026                  2026-05-06 Rajiv Gandhi...
Sunrisers Hyderabad vs Rajasthan Royals, 21st Match, Indian Premier League 2026              2026-04-13 Rajiv Gandhi...
Sunrisers Hyderabad vs Royal Challengers Bengaluru, 67th Match, Indian Premier League 2026   2026-05-22 Rajiv Gandhi...


